All hell moves in.
The Front Room is a horror film directed by Max Eggers.
Everything goes to hell for newly-pregnant Belinda
after her mother-in-law moves in.
As the diabolical guest tries to get her claws on the
child, Belinda must draw the line somewhere.
Belinda, played by Brandy Norwood.
Norman, played by Andrew Burnap.
Solange, played by Kathryn Hunter.
Pastor Lewis, played by Neal Huff.
Old Man, played by David Manis.
Old Woman, played by Mary Catherine Wright.
The Front Room is a 2024 American psychological horror film written and directed by the Eggers Brothers,
in their feature film debut, based on the 2016 short story of the same name by Susan Hill.
The film stars Brandy, Kathryn Hunter, Andrew Burnap, and Neal Huff.
The Front Room was released in the United States by A24 on September 6, 2024.
The film received mixed reviews from critics.
The film explores themes of ku klux klan, mother-in-law,
racism, based on short story, confederate.
The tone is dark and mind_bending.